brandthunder.com 2015-12-11

# Privacy Policy | Brand Thunder

All the legal information you’d expect to see is below, but before you get to that, there’s some other information that we thought you should know. We build these browser themes to make money. Please, don’t hate us.

We’ll never do anything inappropriate. We think too highly of you, our other users, our clients and the brands we represent to ever jeopardize any of those relationships. If we’re doing our jobs well, you’ll love your Internet even more with a Brand Thunder theme and how we help you with shopping assistants, savings tools, advertising or some other means to find you better offers and make a few dollars here and there.

For those who think a free product means free and that living on ramen and public wi-fi is a perfectly good way to run a business – we give those people options and control to adjust how and if we get a chance to earn any revenue. (We really wish they’d also talk to all the brands that want to be paid for using their images. Surprising how much you have to pay to build and giveaway a free product.)

We hope you give us a fair chance to earn something for what we believe is an exceptional product.

**Theme Privacy Policy**

Brand Thunder, LLC (“Brand Thunder”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform users who download a Browser Theme from our websites, www.brandthunder.com, www.thunderthemes.com, and www.bt-engage.com (the “Sites”), about the limited use and disclosure of information generated by the Theme. The Theme may include links or otherwise allow you to access and perhaps submit information to third-party applications or sites.  This Privacy Policy applies to the Theme only.  Any information you submit to linked sites or other applications that may be accessible from the Theme will be subject to the privacy policies of those sites or applications, if any.

You are not required to register with us to download a Theme, and may do so anonymously.  (If you have registered with any of our Sites or have contacted us seeking help, the use and disclosure the information you provided during that process is governed by our general Privacy Policy accessible here.)

**No Spyware, No Adware**

The Theme does not collect any personal information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.). Further, it does not collect or report back to us (or anyone else) any data regarding your computer keystrokes or other data unrelated to the services the Theme provides. To improve your user experience, the Theme or its search partners may analyze search terms or your IP address in order to offer suggested web destinations and targeted advertising for products or services you are interested in. If you enter personal information as a search term, that information may be analyzed in the previously described way.

We may allow third parties to place cookies on our extensions in order to improve your online experience after you leave our extensions. The third party cookies used on our extensions are designed to improve your online experience by facilitating the receipt of targeted advertisements while on our extensions and while you are viewing other websites. These third parties may use information about your visits to our extension and other web sites obtained through their cookie only to provide advertisements for goods and services of interest to you. Other companies’ use of these cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not ours.

Anonymous Theme Usage Statistics.   In order to continue to provide the high-quality Themes to you and to other Users, we do need certain statistics about how our Themes are used.   To facilitate this, the Theme includes one or more unique application numbers that are not associated with you or your Brand Thunder account (if you have chosen to register with us). These numbers are sent to us when you install or uninstall the Theme and when the Theme periodically contacts our servers, for example, to request automatic updates or to provide us with usage statistics about that Theme, such as whether it is active, default settings and total usage of other features of the Theme, including links to third-party applications or sites (“Usage Statistics”).  All Usage Statistics are recorded on a non-personally identifiable basis and is kept strictly anonymous.

Children.  We do not use the Service to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13.   If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at info@brandthunder.com. We will delete such information from our files.

How to Contact Us.  If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, or if you believe there are inaccuracies in your account information you may contact us as follows:

**Brand Thunder, LLC.**

**PO BOX 111**

**Columbus, Ohio 43002**

**Email: info@brandthunder.com**

**Last Updated: February 2012**
